So if we look at ICICI General Insurance, there was
a deep initial dip
but recovery has been made here.  So right now the
strength in this stock is still seen holding out.
But if
we look at National Insurance, a
correction is definitely seen here and the stock has
slipped below its 200 day moving average.
Ah but follow up selling is still missing.
So we feel that the structure here is still
not damaged that much
and we feel that buying will be possible again on the lower side here.
If we talk about ICICI General Insurance, then on the lower side,
it has good support areas around 1900 and 1870.
So unless these levels are
broken, we believe that
buying will return here on dips to the lower side.  On the higher side,
resistance is at 91945.  So
until that level is crossed, the stock will
definitely face some sideways or some pressure on the
higher side.  But the structures are still
not that damaged.  Stocks are still
seen holding support.
Important Levels Your General Insurance
Stocks Pay End of course ICICI LBD
stock is up 1%.  Above 1920 levels.
But now let us look at
PSU banks and it seems that the long term
trend is still intact.
See, after a big rally, some profit
taking has been seen on the higher side.
However, if we look at the structure,
we feel that there is still strength in PSU banks.
If we review the chart of Union Bank
here, it is
seen trading around the 20 day moving average.
We feel that there is still
strength here.
It has important support around 142 140.  As long as this continues,
strength in Union Bank will
remain here and we expect
buying interest to return on dips.   If we
look at the overall behavior of SBI, it is still
displaying sideways behavior.
If we look at the weekly chart, the
stock has been seen trading in a range for almost the last seven to eight weeks.
On the downside, its
lower side support is around 775 780.  And on the higher side, the
stock is facing resistance near 820.
So we think that this
stock will still behave a little sideways.  Unless the
atmosphere of uncertainty ends
from the market.
So this will be a little sideways behavior.  And
then going forward we feel that there
is strength here and there is strength on the long term charts.
So there is a possibility that it will again be
seen breaking out on a higher side.  If it registers a breakout of 820, then
its next targets will again be
seen coming towards 860 870.
If we talk about other PSU banks, then if we
look at the structure of Bank of India, then if we
look at this stock also, then the
stock is travelling in an up sloping channel.
However, in today's dip, the stock has
slipped slightly below the 20-day moving average.  But even now,
if we look here, the 50 day moving
average which is formed around 117 will be
its next support.  So
in decline, the level of 117 will have to be watched here.
If this stock is able to hold that level, then it will
also see a pullback from there.  But
if we look at the other hand, buying interest remains in the NBFC
space and housing finance company space.  There is
a good buying interest in these companies on the lower side.
So banking and financial as a theme is what
we like and we think once the
markets get a little stable again,
we think the BFSI space can
see a continuation of its outperformance.   There
is a bullish view on the BFSI space.
Important tax on SBI and Bank of India from
Rajesh ji.  But there was a block deal of
1.6% equity on Joining Us Now.  It is
believed
that the promoter family will
sell its stake.  But
we will definitely wait for clarification on all these details
because this complete
data will be revealed after the market.  But Rajesh ji, how are
you looking at the charge of Jubilate Food Work?
Because if I look at the technical setup,
it is definitely forming a bullish engulfing, but should we
trust today's rise?
So Shishi ji, see, there is a recovery in the stock
from the lower side and the kind of
structure that has been formed.  We believe the
stock is still expected to struggle slightly around its 50-day moving average.   There
is an immediate resistance area for Ah 690.  The level of 690 will be crossed.  So
we think that a move can be
seen towards 705, 705, 710.  As time goes on,
we think we will see some more consolidation happening
here.
Its immediate support on the downside is around 670.
So we think the stock will be in the range of 670 to 690
and after the breakout of 690,
a good upmove will unfold in the stock.  The
overall structure is bullish
on the stock.  Going forward, we believe a
breakout is definitely coming here.  And then
again targets of 700 plus will be
seen being made in the stock.  So
from a positional perspective, buy accumulation can be done.
Stop loss should be kept around 665.
So technical view on Jilan Food Wax
from Rajesh ji but Nirav has many such
stocks, if we look at them for the whole month i.e. one to one and a half
months, then it is performing well consistently.
In such a situation, tensions have arisen again today
and we already have deals with some nations.
BEL and HL Rajesh ji, please
give your opinion on both of them because
today's trend is also showing both the counters
holding,
how do you see the future trend in such a market, I
think if you look at their trends, then in defense
stocks like BL, HL and other stocks
also, the trends seem to be bullish here
and we feel that in BL, only
a sideways consolidation has been seen in the last two-three weeks.  The
overall structure of the stock
is bullish.  Across all time frames, the
stock is seen trading in a bullish trajectory.
So we feel that as
long as this stock remains above 380, the
trade should be kept on the bullish side and
as soon as this stock succeeds in crossing the level of 300 398 on the upside,
then
its next target should be
towards 415 420.  So BL pay view
is bullish.
Buy and accumulate can be done with stop loss of 390 and stop loss of 380.
If we look at the structure in HL also, then
a sideways consolidation was seen here in the last two-three weeks.  On the
higher side, the resistance in the stock is
around 5150.
When these levels are crossed
then uptick resume will be visible here also.
And then further higher targets
towards 5500 can also be seen coming.   Right now it would be
advisable to buy and accumulate here
until the level of 4900 is
broken on closing basis.  As long as
buy and accumulate can only be done.
And then on the upside, we feel there is a
possibility that the stock may
break out on the higher side going forward.
So here is your opinion on both HL and BEL counters.
But apart from this, which counters
seem to be in focus next week and
will this move be sustained
in such a market?
So, there has definitely been an uptick in the stock,
but if we look at its weekly chart, the
stock has been seen trading in a narrow price range for the last four to five weeks.
However, the stock has
made a good recovery from an oversold treasury and after the recovery, the stock is seen displaying
a sideways behavior for the last four weeks.
We feel that the
immediate hurdle here in the stock is
around the range of 725-730.
If it crosses the level then
a short covering move may be
seen here.  And then the stock will
also see higher targets towards 760.
So
for those who can create a position here from a slightly positional perspective, this
is an attractive price point for Tata Motors.
On the downside, we believe the stock is
comfortably holding out its 50 day or 100 day moving
average.  So, a
little positional at 695, stop loss will have to be kept
around 695 and
when the stock breaks out of 720 on the upside, then a good
rally will unfold.  So we are expecting positional target up
to 760.  Stop loss will be around
695.
All right.  Tata Motors: Keep a stop loss of Rs 695 here with a
target of Rs 760